Finding Aid for Netzorg family papers, late 1800s-2012.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Oversize Material
  Oversize Morton J. and Petra Fuld Netzorg material includes a copy of Morton's diploma from the Xavier University, certificate of appreciation issued by the Rotary Club or Sanu Juan, and oversize scrapbook.
  - Fuld family (Box 37)
  - Morton I. and Katherine Netzorg (Box 37)
  - Morton J. and Petra Fuld Netzorg (Box 37)
- Artifacts
  The Artifacts series contains Bracha Fuld's military ribbon, Morton I. Netzorg's USO patch and three armbands from Santo Tomas Internment Camp accompanied by a letter explaining Japanese writing on the armbands.
  - Bracha Fuld
    - Military ribbon (Box 37)
  - Morton I. Netzorg
    - USO patch (Box 37)
    - Three Japanese armbands with accompanying material (Box 37)
Related Material
Researchers should note that the Bentley Historical Library holds a separate collection of Morton J. Netzorg papers that contains source material collected as part of National Endowment for Humanities study of children's literature in the Philippine Islands. Also audio recordings of Jock Netzorg interviews, conducted by Michael P. Onorato in 1987.